{
    "id": "f28719ed4cbc4ef2a46da36212dc2b52",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went ………………………. on the weekend.",
            "description": "There is no preposition in the expression go swimming, go walking, go climbing etc.",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "to swimming",
                "Either could be used here",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go ………………………… drive next weekend.",
            "description": "This is a common expression referring to leisure activities.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "for a",
                "to a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I went swimming ………………………… the sea.",
            "description": "Prepositions of place are used after go + …ing.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t go skating ………………………….. the lake.",
            "description": "Prepositions of place are used after go + …ing.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We went shopping ……………………… Dubai.",
            "description": "Prepositions of place are used after go + …ing.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. mend her ways.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice.",
            "answers": [
                "has better",
                "had better",
                "have better"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Half of my friends ……………………… abroad.",
            "description": "When the noun following half of is plural, we use a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "living"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had scarcely closed my eyes ………………………. I heard a knock on the door.",
            "description": "Scarcely is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I closed the door ………………………….. someone knocked.",
            "description": "We use than after no sooner.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was hardly inside the house ………………………… the lights went out.",
            "description": "Hardly is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She had no sooner agreed to marry him than she ……………………… having serious doubts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "started",
                "was starting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}